Good buddy Leonard?
- What do you want?
- Hey, good buddy.
So I was just talking to Amy...
(Sheldon:)...and she made me realize
that this little dust-up...
(Sheldon:)...between you and me
is much ado about nothing.
- Is that so?
- Yes. All is forgiven, so come back home.
(Sheldon:)I'll make you some soy hot chocolate
and then I'll tell you about...
(Sheldon:)...our exciting new
devil-may-care bathroom policy.
(Leonard:)Cut to the chase, Sheldon.
Okay. Amy has decided
she wants to move in with me...
(Sheldon:)...so I need you to come back home,
you lovable scamp.
(Sheldon:)That's a lot of product.
- Hey. What's going on?
- Get this.
(Leonard:)Suddenly, Sheldon wants me back
because Amy wants to move in with him.
(Penny:)Really? Interesting.
(Leonard:)Well, too late, pal, I'm not going anywhere.
(Leonard:)Penny and I are very happy living together.
Isn't that right?
(Penny:)It's like the happiness
won't ever leave the apartment.